<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-30T00:38:07-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Steve’s Blog</title><subtitle>Writings about projects and interests</subtitle><author><name>Stephen Mahon</name></author><entry><title type="html">Test</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/30/test.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test" /><published>2022-12-30T00:18:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-12-30T00:18:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/12/30/test</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/12/30/test.html"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>Stephen Mahon</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to my blog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2021/10/03/welcome-to-my-blog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to my blog" /><published>2021-10-03T02:23:16-05:00</published><updated>2021-10-03T02:23:16-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2021/10/03/welcome-to-my-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2021/10/03/welcome-to-my-blog.html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my blog. I’m not sure what content will populate these pages just yet, but it will be related to the day-to-day activites of my life. Currently I am working on a couple of woodworking projects, several coding endevours including some ML work and backend stuff, systems engineering and systems thinking, and my side-hustle.</p>

<p>I’ve been actively applying for job the last several months. I completed my viva voce for my doctorate work in March 2021. I took some time off and worked on patents I developed during my time at university. Some of that work is in the process of spinning out of the university. While I developed the underlying technology during my postgrad and postdoc, I have very little to do with the activitis of the company. I serve as a consulant to the executive staff. I fleshed out the patents in a Makerspace in St Charles, IL called <a href="fox.build">Fox.Build</a>.</p>

<p>The last summer has been filled with the exploration of my new home. I am very happy to have immigrated to the United States late 2020. I’ve endured the wicked Winters and scorching Summer of the Midwest. As we head into Fall I will reflect on my experiences as an immigrant over the last 12 months.</p>

<p>This year I’ve adopted a strenuous lifestyle inspired by the livelhood of the 26th President of the United States, Theodore Roosevelt. The Strenuous Life explores living while actively pursuing hard things. The program include daily exercise, good deeds, and encouraging compadre relationships amoung other like-valued individuals. I will deleve into my year and future in the arena here.</p>

<p>I started woodworking after many years away from handtools and chisels. I was an advid study of tactile subjects in my youth. I attended a technical (junior/high) school for preparing apprentices for skilled work. I even trained with a tiler and considered dropping out of high school to presure a career in bespoke residential jobs. I started woodworking this past year at my makerspace and with the optics of strenuous activity. I’ve designed some furniture, include the desk I am using right now. Expect some content on that.</p>

<p>I’m not sure what my expectations are just yet but I’m keen to document some of my thinkings, works in progress, hopefully completed projects, and lessons learned along the way.</p>

<p>-Steve</p>]]></content><author><name>Stephen Mahon</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to my blog. I’m not sure what content will populate these pages just yet, but it will be related to the day-to-day activites of my life. Currently I am working on a couple of woodworking projects, several coding endevours including some ML work and backend stuff, systems engineering and systems thinking, and my side-hustle.]]></summary></entry></feed>